FUGITIVES, FRIENDS AND FOREVER BROTHERS.
We Bare Bears: The Movie is a animation, adventure,
family film directed by Daniel Chong.
When Grizz, Panda, and Ice Bear's love of food trucks and viral videos get out of hand, the brothers are now
chased away from their home and embark on a trip to Canada, where they can live in peace.
Grizzly (voice), played by Eric Edelstein.
Panda (voice), played by Bobby Moynihan.
Ice Bear (voice), played by Demetri Martin.
Agent Trout (voice), played by Marc Evan Jackson.
Charlie (voice), played by Jason Lee.
Nom Nom (voice), played by Patton Oswalt.
We Bare Bears: The Movie is a 2020 American animated adventure comedy film
based on the Cartoon Network television series of the same name.
Produced by Cartoon Network Studios and directed by series creator Daniel Chong from a story by Mikey Heller and Kris Mukai, We Bare Bears: The Movie stars the voices of series regulars Eric
Edelstein, Bobby Moynihan, and Demetri Martin as the three titular bears Grizzly, Panda, and Ice Bear; joined by Marc Evan Jackson as Agent Trout and Keith Ferguson as Officer Murphy.
This film serves as the series finale of We Bare Bears.
In their desire to be accepted into the community, the three bear brothers Grizzly, Panda, and Ice Bear unwittingly
wreak havoc throughout the San Francisco Bay Area, igniting a mob of complaints from its residents.
Seeking to remove them from society, wildlife control agent Trout relentlessly pursues to
separate the brothers, who in turn escape from the Bay Area and seek refuge in Canada.
Along the way, the Bears endure hardships while staying true
to their promise of being "bros for life".
The film was released on North American digital
theater platforms by Warner Bros.
Television Distribution on June 30, 2020, and had its television
premiere on Cartoon Network on September 7, 2020.
Upon its release, We Bare Bears: The Movie received a positive response from film critics, who praised the film's relevant presentation
of its themes, sense of humour, and positive messages, with many calling it an excellent conclusion to the franchise.
Following the conclusion of the series and the film, a spin-off television series titled We
Baby Bears, which follows the Bears as cubs, released on January 1, 2022.
The film explores themes of canada, grizzly bear,
villain, polar bear, road trip.
The tone is lighthearted.